[theme music playing]
[tense music playing]
[screaming]
[shattering sound]
Arnaldo, Arnaldo.
Arnaldo, you're not crazy. Do you hear me?
I won't let you throw away
everything I've done for you.
[maid] Ma'am Emilia!
-[Emilia screams]
-Arnaldo!
[gunshot]
[Julio] Ivy, Arnaldo…
Arnaldo is in the hospital.
He's fighting for his life.
[Ivy] You don't deserve to die,
Arnaldo. You need to live.
I'm not through with the Ardientes.
You have to accept the fact
that Arnaldo is not well!
[Julio] No one tells
Julio Ardiente what to do!
[Ivy] I have decided.
I will go back to Arnaldo
and take care of him.
[Julio] Without Ivy, Arnaldo will die.
You will accept the fact that
Miss Aguas is here to stay.
[Camia] Now that you're
going after Emilia,
it's my right as your mother
to know about all your plans.
I'll strip her of her wealth
and family name.
I'm sure that the Ardientes will do
everything for Arnaldo to get well,
but I won't make it easy for them.
I won't let Arnaldo
get back on his feet again.
[Natalie] I know you want
something from me.
I saw that Arnaldo is getting sick.
Let's not kid ourselves.
[Raul] Fine. Eight o'clock.
The usual place.
A public announcement.
We just need to make
a public announcement as well.
A press conference, Congressman.
That's what we'll do.
What? A press conference?
Do you want people to talk about
Arnaldo's suicide attempt?
You're out of your mind! Where's Raul?
You shouldn't be looking
for someone who's not here
because I'm sure he's busy
with someone else.
We don't need him.
Raul is Arnaldo's father.
Obviously, his opinion matters
more than yours.
Let Ivy speak.
Thank you, Congressman.
My plan is to not announce
what really happened to Arnaldo.
The key is taking control
of the situation.
We'll just tell them
what needs to be said.
-Miss Aguas is right.
-Hmm?
What's important is for us to mold
the people's opinion of Arnaldo.
Schedule a press conference.
I have an announcement to make.
[tense music playing]
Anna. Are you okay?
You seemed angry earlier.
Do you know how painful it is
to find out Arnaldo's case
was dismissed and he's free now?
Diego, he killed my foster mother…
along with my dreams
we all had for ourselves.
He also killed my friend. And many others.
You know, Anna, even as kids,
Arnaldo treated me like dirt,
like we weren't brothers.
It's easy to get angry and retaliate,
but we have to watch our actions.
We'll attain justice the right way.
One day, he'll pay for his crimes.
Congressman, according
to the camp of Diego Torillo,
Camia, and Lily Cruz,
they won't stop until
Mayor Arnaldo is behind bars.
What can you say about this?
To my beloved children,
the citizens of Poblacion Ardiente,
this is the first time
I'll face you like this.
With a heavy and broken heart.
Because your beloved mayor is gravely ill.
[reporter] Care to be specific,
Congressman?
[Julio] I don't want to go
into the specifics.
All I can tell you is,
Arnaldo will be on
an indefinite sick leave.
And in the meantime,
I kindly ask everyone to pray
for his speedy recovery.
So, who will be the acting mayor?
And what about his candidacy?
[Julio] We will follow the rule of law.
The vice mayor shall be the acting mayor.
As soon as Arnaldo is discharged
from the hospital,
he will continue
campaigning
for his candidacy
as our next governor.
Again, to all the citizens
of Poblacion Ardiente,
who I regard as my children,
our family is once again going
through another rough patch.
But despite this,
we thank all of you for your
never-ending support for us.
Let's all keep praying
for our mayor.
Viva Ardiente!
His interview is trending on social media.
According to one user, "I feel
sorry for Congressman Ardiente.
Clearly, he loves his grandson."
-Let me see.
-Look at all these posts!
Here's another one.
"I hope Mayor Arnaldo gets well soon so
our beloved congressman will cheer up."
[Pandoy exclaims]
Obviously, they're looking for sympathy.
-[Marlon] Typical.
-Here's another one.
"Poor mayor, he's sick.
I'll vote for him as governor."
-[man] Geez!
-[Marlon] They all pity him.
[man 2] Looks like it.
This is bad.
We need to get these people
to sympathize with us.
We'll re-file the charges as planned.
And we'll continue our campaign.
Let's remind the public that
this happened to their mayor
not because he should be pitied,
but because he deserved it.
He must be imprisoned for all his crimes!
[tense music playing]
Jepoy, the Ardientes
are playing with the situation.
Even though Arnaldo's crimes
were made public,
they can get the sympathy of the people.
To think they feel sorry for
a family of soulless murderers
and expressed support for Arnaldo!
Jepoy, I'm worried
that Arnaldo might get away
with what he did to Aunt Carlotta!
[door closing]
[reporter] In other news,
a woman hanged herself
in Poblacion Ardiente.
She was later identified
as Carlotta Navarro,
caretaker of businesswoman, Ivy Aguas.
This has been Dennis Pangilinan,
reporting for ATV.
[cries]
Auntie!
Auntie Carlotta!
Anna?
[Anna] Jepoy, Auntie is dead!
[grunts]
Jepoy, Auntie is dead! Jepoy…
[Anna] Jepoy, we made a promise
that day, remember?
We swore to help each other.
Help me take revenge on Arnaldo.
Anna, that was not part of our agreement.
That's not part of our plans.
But, Jepoy, everything we're
fighting for will be for nothing
if Arnaldo stays in power.
I can't let him become the next governor!
Fine.
So, what's your plan?
Thank you, miss. We'll go now.
Thank you so much, sir.
[suspenseful music playing]
Yes, ma'am?
-Room 272?
-Okay, ma'am.
Here, ma'am. Thank you so much.
Thank you.
[Emilia] This is all Ivy's fault.
She's behind this press conference.
And how can you not have
a statement, Papa?
Vice Mayor Romero? Are you kidding me?
He is the rightful acting mayor,
as far as the law of the land
is concerned,
while Arnaldo is still in the hospital.
And one more thing.
Nobody's going to replace
Arnaldo in the election.
When Arnaldo wins the governorship,
I should be the mayor of this town, Papa.
Especially now that I have
an annulment case ongoing,
I have all the time for public service.
Hmm…
You may have the time,
but you left out one thing.
Intelligence. That position needs a brain.
I used to be the governor
and mayor of this town, Papa.
Stress on the words "used to."
Don't be so surprised
that you've been demoted.
Don't even be proud of your term
of office because, to be honest,
you didn't accomplish anything
except for being an embarrassment
and a landfill of dead bodies
of the people you killed.
How about the billion-peso fund
that I gave this family
while I was the mayor of this town?
Maybe, Papa, you should put that
in my accomplishments.
You should give credit to where it's due.
How will you handle a city's problems…
if you can't even handle your husband?
Fix your marriage,
and then come back to me.
[scoffs]
WE NEED TO TALK. IT'S IMPORTANT!
[tense music playing]
[heart monitor beeping rhythmically]
Do you know how long I've waited
for this opportunity?
If a person's heart is full of anger
and thoughts of revenge…
that person can do things they
never thought they could do.
[suspenseful music]
[suspenseful music continues]
[heart monitor beeping rhythmically]
[door opens]
[door closes]
Nurse, has Emilia stopped by yet?
[suspenseful music continues]
Nurse? Did the Ardientes stop by?
-[suspenseful music continues]
-[heart monitor beeping]
Anna!
Let go of me.
-Lily, let go of me.
-Shh… Keep it down.
What are you doing?
What are you planning to do?
Let me avenge Nanny Carlotta's death!
That monster needs to pay.
You don't need to do that.
-Ivy. Pick up the phone.
-[line ringing]
You need to stop Anna.
-Let me do this! Let go!
-I won't let you do this.
-Let go!
-Anna, I won't let you do this.
Put that thing down.
Let me do this, Ivy. Let go of me.
Let go--
I will kill this monster--
[Anna groans]
[tense music playing]
-[line ringing]
-Ivy!
This is going to get us in trouble!
You're actually going against me now?
[cries]
-[sighs]
-[Anna crying]
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, Lily. Sorry! I'm so sorry!
-I'm sorry.
-[shushes]
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
[shushes] Calm down.
[Jepoy] What has gotten into you, Anna?!
Why did you do that?
What were you thinking?!
Think about what would've
happened if they caught you.
You're a teacher, right?
What would've happened to you
if they had caught you?
Lily, I lost my old life
when I decided to come here
and assume your identity.
-Anna.
Do you think I can easily
go back to my old life
after I pretended to be Lily Cruz?!
How can I continue living
when all I can think about
is that the man
who murdered my foster mother
hasn't been punished yet?!
Why?! Did I ask you
to assume my identity?!
Did I beg you to?!
You both chose that, right?
You wanted that to happen, remember?
Anna, I know you're affected.
And I respect that.
But I take responsibility
for everything that happened.
I am doing everything to seek justice.
I plan everything carefully.
I think about my every move.
But what did you do?
You could've ruined all of it.
As a matter of fact, Anna,
I could easily hurt all of them.
I could easily kill them all,
but I refuse to do it
because I don't want to be like them.
Because I am not a murderer.
We are not murderers!
You want justice?
You want to seek justice?!
If you want justice,
then learn to cooperate.
I'm telling you, Anna,
don't go against me!
Because the next time you do
something without telling me,
I don't know what I'll do to you!
Get your act together.
[Diego] All right, calm down.
We're all here to fix the problem.
We're not here to fight.
We should try to be more understanding.
[Anna sobbing]
[Emilia] Papa is short-sighted.
He's an amnesiac.
Why do I have to patch things
up with Raul just to get back
into power, Jaguar?
You know, I don't get it.
[sighs]
Can you just help me plan a plot?
A coup against my Papa?
Why don't you give your husband
another chance?
[sighs] Because I don't love Raul anymore.
I can only think of you.
I can see us together, Jaguar.
[exhales]
I'm sorry, Emilia.
Hello? Jaguar?
Why did you have to be so stubborn?
Haven't you learned from my mistakes?
[Anna sobs]
I know I said some harsh words to Anna.
But I'm only thinking
about your well-being.
[Jepoy] Anna.
I didn't mean to shout at you earlier.
No, Jepoy. It's my fault. [sniffles]
I should've listened to Lily and to you.
Ivy, Anna looks up to you.
I'm sure she understands.
Besides, you're best friends.
Everything will be all right.
I'm sorry, Jepoy. I hope you forgive me.
I hope Lily can still forgive me.
Hush now. Stop crying.
-Mom, I have to go.
-Take care, dear.
-Diego.
-Take care, Ivy.
Please take care of them.
I will.
[soft music playing]
Lily.
[soft music continues]
I'm sorry.
Sorry!
[soft music continues]
Poor little Raul.
Who would've thought
that you'd be involved
in a love triangle between you,
Emilia, and another version of yourself?
Isn't that crazy? It's so twisted!
And, it's so exciting.
But you know what?
What's more exciting
is your annulment with Emilia.
There won't be an annulment.
What are you saying?
That you'll choose Emilia over me?
Wait. Choose? Why do I have to choose now?
Aren't we just helping each other?
We're just using each other.
-Yes.
-So?
But, I'm selfish.
What's mine is mine.
You. You're all mine.
Even if we're just using each other.
[tense music playing]
[club music playing]
Emilia. You're here. Good evening.
There's nothing good about it.
Are you really not going
to leave me alone?
Do you really want to go against me?
I know we fight about a lot of things.
And we've even tried to have
each other killed lots of times.
But, in the end, we get along.
Yes. Do you know why?
It's hard to eliminate you.
Until now, you're still here.
I can't get rid of you.
Admit it, Emilia.
I could be of some use to you.
I have information.
And I know, you'll be interested.
Lunch tomorrow?
[tense music playing]
You should've seen your mom's face.
[scoffs]
She was blaming Ivy
for convincing me
to hold that press conference.
Silly little girls!
They both think they can outwit
and manipulate me.
[scoffs]
[suspenseful music playing]
You're really testing my patience, Ivy.
Excuse me?
Don't act as if I don't know.
It's pretty obvious. [chuckles]
Lately, I noticed that Papa
has been taking your side.
First, Arnaldo's psych counseling.
Second, the press conference.
What are you trying to prove?
That you're the apple of Papa's eye?!
But you still came here.
Don't get jealous, Emilia. It's all right.
Emilia, we don't have to be friends.
But we do have to get along
if we want to protect
each other's interests.
Actually, I'm the one
who should be mad at you.
You wanted to have me killed
on my wedding day, remember?
But, here I am,
trying to let go of that issue
because Arnaldo is more important to me.
I don't believe you've forgiven
Arnaldo for killing
that mother figure of yours.
And I especially
don't believe you love him.
I won't waste my time
trying to convince you.
What do you know about love, Ivy?
What about you?
You have no moral ascendancy.
You're getting an annulment, right?
How dare you?!
Careful.
If I were you, I would stop
playing hard to get,
because Raul might grow tired
of chasing after you,
and he might start pursuing other women.
-I don't care!
-Really?
[tense music playing]
Natalie and Raul are together in a hotel.
Hmm… What could they
possibly be doing there?
[tense music playing]
Your husband is fooling you again.
But, that's okay. You're getting
an annulment anyway, right?
What pleasure do you get
from seeing me getting hurt?
Are you still affected by it?
I thought it didn't mean anything
to you anymore. Sorry.
But that really is
what I wanted to show you.
I will tear that woman into pieces.
That, I'll surely do.
[tense music playing]
Colonel, any updates?
Congressman, I've already dealt
with the reporters
trying to ruin the mayor's reputation.
They kept asking when he'll recover.
He'll wake up soon.
My grandson has an iron will…
a campaign to run, and an election to win.
What do you plan to do with Diego Torillo?
He's starting up a ruckus again.
Just say the word.
My men are ready.
Not so fast, Colonel.
Contrary to what people believe,
I do have a sense of diplomacy.
Send a message to Diego Torillo.
We need to talk.
Yes, sir.
-Will that be okay?
-Yes, sir.
Hold on, are we expecting someone?
[man] No.
-Soldiers?
-Be alert.
[tense music playing]
Wait.
You're armed. What are you doing here?
I'm not here to cause trouble.
I have a message
from Congressman Ardiente
for Diego Torillo.
-Oh.
-Call them.
Yes, Jepoy.
[tense music playing]
[Loring] What's this?
[Diego] Nanny.
I'm Diego Torillo. Why are you here?
Congressman Ardiente asked me
to give you this.
[tense music playing]
WE HAVE LOTS TO DISCUSS.
LET'S MEET AT THE PLAZA LATER.
PLEASE GRANT MY REQUEST.
CONGRESSMAN JULIO ARDIENTE
The congressman wants to meet with me.
[Loring] Don't even think
of granting that request.
-That might be a trap.
-They're right, Diego.
I won't fall for their trap.
If the congressman wants
to talk, then I won't back down.
Diego, I'll come with you.
[Marlon] Batch.
[Raul] Let's just do that. Let's meet up.
Okay, I'll call you later. Thank you.
[tense music playing]
[phone ringing]
I HAVE A SURPRISE FOR YOU.
LET'S MEET. SAME TIME AND PLACE.
Prove to me that you're on my side.
Join me in this war I'm going into.
I don't have to prove anything, Emilia.
But I'll go with you just for fun.
Great. Let's go.
I'm here.
Raul? Ooh.
You really set it up nicely, huh?
Raul?
Did you miss me?
Surprise!
[laughs] Why am I not surprised?
-Do you want a surprise?
-[Natalie grunts]
You snot-nosed bitch.
[chuckles]
[foreboding music playing]
-This way.
-A reporter.
Congressman Julio! We'd like
to ask a few questions!
Are you here to see Diego Torillo?
-Congressman!
-Here for Diego Torillo?
-Congressman Julio…
-Any statement?
Congressman!
[reporter] Mr. Diego, thoughts
on the congressman's visit?
Boys.
Diego, Diego, Diego…
You didn't need to bring
the whole village.
You even brought Lily Cruz too.
Oh! And Madrigal!
You look a lot better
than the last time I saw you.
What do you need?
Diego, for now, I'd like you to refrain
from refiling charges against Arnaldo.
[scoffs]
I'm afraid I can't give you
what you're asking for.
[tut-tuts]
You know, we're starting
on the wrong foot again.
You don't understand.
What I'm telling you
is not a request. It's an order.
[tense music playing]
[Natalie] Emilia and Ivy?
No way! [laughs]
This is fun! I'm impressed!
So, this kinda seems familiar. Right?
Yes, Natalie.
The three little witches meet again.
-[Natalie scoffs]
-But this time, you're the one tied up.
What was that again?
You know, I have trouble remembering.
Was that…
[laughs]
No, it doesn't suit me.
Could you hold this for me, Ivy?
Was that, um…
-[Emilia] One slap? Two slaps?
-[Natalie grunts]
And the third one will be for
you sleeping with my husband!
[laughs]
I missed you too, Emilia. But guess what?
The fact of the matter is, I'm back.
And I slept with him,
and am sleeping,
and will be sleeping with him
until I forget how to bend over!
[Emilia grunts]
-Emilia. Emilia, calm down.
-Do it.
-Emilia, no.
-Calm down?! Calm down?!
I am so sick and tired of people
telling me to calm down!
-I am so tired!
-[gunshot]
-I've had enough!
-[gunshots]
Emilia!
[screams] I don't want to calm down now!
You think Ivy Aguas is on your side.
But you know that from the start,
she has been your worst enemy!
She successfully snaked your son Arnaldo
and made him fall in love.
And now, she left him for dead!
And guess who she's coming after?
You!
[tense music playing]
Try it.
See if you can pull the trigger
before I bash your face.
[Emilia screaming]
-Enough! Enough!
-[gunshot]
[Emilia screaming]
-Stop it!
-You're crazy!
-So what if I'm crazy?!
-Emilia!
So what if I'm crazy?!
Don't kill that woman.
I'm just here for fun, remember?
If you kill her, I won't
help you clean up her body.
Be thankful I'm not one
for cleaning messes.
If I was, I'd end you now.
But I'm warning you.
If you sleep with my husband
again, I will kill you.
I will definitely kill you!
Oops. [chuckles]
I forgot something. I need a souvenir.
Give me your best smile.
[Emilia] Ugh.
[laughs]
You're crazy! Nutjob!
That's right! Since the start! [laughs]
[Emilia laughing]
Congratulations, Natalie.
You're still alive.
Thank me next time.
[dramatic music]
Where are you going?
Bye.
Ivy? Hey!
Don't leave me here, you two witches!
You're both nuts!
Do you actually think
I'll let you kick Arnaldo while he's down?
You're blind to your own arrogance.
You think everyone who isn't
an Ardiente is dumb.
But the truth is,
you're the only ones
who still believe you're smart.
This town is spitting you out.
My, strong words. Can you back them up?
I'm running for governor
so that the common people
have a voice against people like you.
That's why Arnaldo will pay
for all his crimes,
whether he likes it or not.
Okay, suit yourself
if you want to play the small-town hero
that you've always aspired to be.
But don't tell me
I didn't warn you, Diego.
You're going up against a behemoth.
You're going up against me.
And after the battle,
when the smoke has cleared,
your death will be very biblical.
To paraphrase a line in the Old Testament,
"I will reduce you to ashes and dust."
Miss Lily Cruz.
Finally, I get to meet you.
Television doesn't do you justice.
You look better in person. [chuckles]
Oh, well.
[tense music playing]
Excuse me. My, my.
Madrigal, what a big gun you have.
Ooh!
Jepoy.
Please?
[scoffs]
Amateurs. I'm going up against amateurs.
[reporter] Congressman Julio! Sir!
[indistinct chatter]
[reporter] Mr. Diego, what did you
and Congressman Julio talk about?
[Camia] Is it true that the Ardientes
stole this farmland from your forefathers?
Yes, Miss Camia.
Ivy Aguas was supposed
to set up a business here.
But she backed out because
of the rights of the farmers.
Do you know any other scandals
or corrupt activities of the Ardientes?
It's scary to speak out.
Their loyalists might find out.
But somebody over there can help.
As far as I know, she used to be
an employee at city hall,
when Emilia Ardiente was still the mayor.
-Where does she live?
-Right down the road.
-Okay, thank you.
-Okay. Let's go.
I told you, Emilia.
We don't need to be friends
just to have fun.
So, Ivy, why don't you sponsor
my candidacy?
Maybe someday, we could be running mates.
Isn't that exciting?
You're trying to sell me something again?
Tell me, Emilia.
Why should I enter politics?
Because in politics, it's like a jungle.
Just hesitate,
and you'll get bitten by snakes.
I don't need to enter politics
to know that.
Okay, okay, okay.
Politics is something
beyond what you can imagine.
You can get anything that you like.
It has its own perks, Ivy.
And you can actually steal billions.
[laughs] Oh, shoot.
Billions?
That's supposed to be a secret, okay?
Lips are sealed. Cheers. Lips are sealed!
[laughing]
-[Diego] Nanny, Uncle.
-[Loring] Thank goodness…
-Diego.
-you're back safe…
-and sound. Oh, my.
-Yes, son.
That old man's this close
to meeting his maker,
-and he still hasn't changed!
-[Pandoy laughs]
But you know, Miss Loring,
Diego was pretty cool earlier.
He faced Julio Ardiente head on!
Yeah, he never backs down
from a challenge.
[laughs] Still, you should
be careful, son.
Julio's a cunning man!
-Of course, Uncle. Don't worry.
-Yes.
By the way, where's Auntie Camia?
Oh, she had some errand
at the cooperative.
-Um… Excuse me.
-Yes?
Do you know where Miss Cora lives?
Oh, yes. Over there. The lady sweeping.
-Oh, thank you.
-No problem.
Excuse me, is this where Miss Cora lives?
Oh, that's me. And, you are?
I'm Camia Cruz.
Oh, aren't you the one
supporting Diego Torillo for governor?
Yes. I was hoping to ask you
some questions if that's okay.
About what?
About the Ardientes.
I heard you served as Emilia's secretary
when she was still mayor.
Oh, my, that was such a long time ago.
Actually, I was hoping you could help me.
I'm sorry.
But, I still have lots of chores to do.
[no audio]
You liar! Cheater!
You're still sleeping with Natalie.
Hold on. What? Emilia, where'd you hear?
-No!
-Wait.
Here! So, stop lying to me!
I saw everything! I caught you red-handed!
Raul…
You don't want to file for annulment,
you don't want to sign the papers,
and yet, you're still cheating on me!
-Wait, wait, wait!
-No, I've had it!
-Emilia, wait!
-Enough is enough!
-I've had enough.
-Wait.
-Let me explain! Emilia, please. Emilia!
-No! No.
-No.
-Not like this, Emilia…
-No!
-Let's talk this through.
-Enough talk, Raul!
-Please.
-We're over, Raul!
-Please, stop.
No! You, get out of my house!
And you get out of my life!
We're over, Raul.
-Emilia.
-I've had enough!
-I'm sorry.
-I've had it.
Emilia… Emilia!
[heart monitor beeping]
[Emilia] Arnaldo?
[exhales] Son! You're awake! You're awake!
He's awake now.
Papa, he's awake!
[tense music playing]
Miss Cora, I'm begging you.
Please help us.
We could really use your statement.
It would be a big help to us.
Aren't you afraid I might tell
the Ardientes what you're doing?
Miss Cora, I'm just taking a chance.
Even just a lead.
Maybe you can give us something,
so we'll know where to start.
Are you sure you don't work
for the Ardientes?
[sighs]
We're victims
of the Ardientes too, Miss Cora.
I'm doing this so that, one day,
the citizens of this town
can break free
from the Ardientes' tyranny.
So, I hope you'll help us.
[doctor] The mayor needs to
undergo consultation
psychiatric before we discharge him.
And we need to do this, or else,
his condition could worsen.
How long will this all take, doc?
The results of the assessment
will depend on his reaction to the tests.
Blah, blah, blah, blah, blah,
blah, blah. Look at him go.
Doc, my grandson is well. Can't you see?
His brain is as tough as anything can get.
Now, please, could you please
just release him from this dreary place?
But, Congressman--
Doc, your parents sent you
to medical school for 10 years.
After 10 years, you had
an internship and whatnot.
And diagnosis, prognosis, and… [inhales]
…whatever nose-in, nose-out
you talk about.
Anyway, don't put your studies to waste.
Because if I lose my patience,
I might just have your license pulled.
[Julio sighs]
-[muffled scream]
-[Arnaldo grunting]
-[Arnaldo] What about her?
-You shouldn't trust her.
[Arnaldo] That's not true.
That's not true.
[Nimfa] She's the one feeding
information to Diego's camp.
That's not true.
[Nimfa] She's Diego's spy
within the Ardiente family!
She's just using you.
[Nimfa] Mayor, you need to know
that Ivy is--
-That's not true!
-[gunshots]
-[Arnaldo screaming]
[gasps]
[door opening]
Ivy. Just… Just stay there.
Stay there.
-Don't come near me. Don't.
-Mayor?
Don't come any closer! Stay there!
-Stay there!
-Mayor, what's wrong?
-Don't touch me!
-Mayor.
Don't touch me!
-Help is coming--
-Don't touch me!
-Doc, nurse, help!
-Mayor, no!
-Don't touch me! [grunts]
-Mayor! Mayor! Mayor, no!
-[nurse grunts]
-Don't touch me!
Don't… Don't touch me!
[groaning]
[tense music playing]
Where are you taking me?
[doctor] The mayor is dangerous.
That's why we moved him
to the psychiatric ward.
[Julio] You'll get better. But not here.
You will spend time in our rest house.
[Arnaldo] I want Ivy to come with me.
[Diego] Arnaldo isn't thinking straight.
Get out of there.
I'm going to finish this.
You shouldn't trust Ivy Aguas.
She's been lying to you.
You shouldn't trust that woman.
[theme music playing]